so this is our continuing solution for
this multi-part quiz
we have begun issuing instruction
malforce so the question is now
what goes into the fields of the
reservation station
and also which rat entry is going to be
modified the modification of the right
entry is going to be easy because it's
going to be the route entry for r1 so
the correct answer here is r1 the rat
entry for r1 is going to be modified and
we modified with rob4 before we do that
however we need to read out what is the
rat content for r1 and r2 and we find
that it's rob2 and rob1 so the answer
here is going to be that this
reservation station entry
for the multiplication is going to have
two tags for r1 rob2 for r2 rob1 and
it's not going to have either of the
values we would only put something here
if we could actually get the actual
value from wherever it is but because we
need to wait for rob2 to get the value
and we need to wait for rob 1 to get
that value which simply leave this empty
so that concludes the correct answering
for this part of the quiz